

+48-505637986

argikartika@gmail.com

github.com/artikandri codepen.io/artikandri codewars.com/users/artikandri

Wrocław, PL

EDUCATION

Master of Engineering Politechnika Wrocławska | Poland

Bachelor of Engineering Universitas Gadjah Mada | Indonesia GPA 3.59/4

Hokkaido University | Japan exchange program

EXPERTISE

HTML (3+ years) HTML5, Pug

Javascript (3+ years)

JS Frameworks (Vue.js, Angular, React), server side development (Nuxt), testing (Jest, Cypress), type-safe dev (Typescripts), documentation (Storybook), other libraries (JQuery, Axios, Lodash, i18n, moment, etc.), clean code (eslint, prettier), Grunt

CSS (3+ years)
Vanilla CSS, SASS/SCSS, LESS, CSS Frameworks
(Bootstrap, Vuetify, Quasar), TailwindCSS, Bulma

Python (1+ year)

Data engineering (pandas, numpy), data visualization (Dash, Plotly), DL/ML (PyTorch, Transformers, sklearn), data scraping (BeautifulSoup, Selenium)

Web & Graphic Design (3+ years)

Photoshop, Figma, Balsamiq, Canva

Containerization (1+ year)

Others (< 1 year)

PHP, React Native, Flutter, Java, Ruby on Rails

LANGUAGE

Polish (A2) English (C1) Indonesia (Native) Japanese (N4)

PUBLICATION

StudEmo: A Non-aggregated Review Dataset for Personalized Emotion Recognition (Ngo et al., NLPerspectives 2022)

ARGI CANDRI

Front End Developer

ABOUT ME

Hello, I am an experienced front-end developer with nearly 4 years of expertise particularly in front end development with **Vue**.js. I have solid experiences in testing (Jest, Cypress), server-side dev (Nuxt), containerization (Docker), REST API (Axios), with some knowledges of other FW (Angular, React), w/wo Typescripts and w/wo CSS frameworks. In my spare time, I enjoy learning about Japanese culture, sparring at Codewars and playing Candy Crush 😘

WORK EXPERIENCE

Clarin-PL | Poland | 2022 - Present Software Developer (Python, Vue.is)

- Collaborating with the backend team and researchers on text annotation tools for affective NLP and human feedback tasks.
- Working on multiple DL/ML projects in the NLP field (multi-task model and emotion recognition) to process data, develop ML models, and visualize results.
- Creating scraper bots for multiple websites using Beautiful Soup + Selenium.
- Developing and maintaining interfaces using Vue + SCSS + Typescript
- Administering DB and deployments using Python, SQLite, ElasticSearch and Docker

Mamikos.com | Indonesia | 2020

Senior Front End Developer (Vue.js)

- ullet Collaborating with the product team, backend team, designers, and testers on ullethouse rental system in a fast-paced environment, using Scrum and delivering results in iterative cycles with a QDD (Quality-Driven Development) approach.
- Developing and maintaining interfaces using Vue + SCSS
- Creating and maintaining unit tests using Jest.

Hrmlabs.com | Adeptforms.com | Indonesia | 2018 - 2022

Front End Developer (Vue.is, JQuery, React Native)

- Collaborating with the backend team on a human resource management system and a form management system in a fast-paced environment.
- Designing, developing, and maintaining interfaces on PHP based web apps and native SPA web apps using Vue.js + SCSS + JQuery
- Developing and maintaining mobile apps using React Native
- Mentoring and providing guidance to interns and new hires, assisting them in comprehending the codebase and development processes.

Indonesia | 2017 - 2018

Freelance (JQuery)

• Designing and developing Wordpress-themed websites (JQuery, Vanilla CSS)

ACHIEVEMENTS

Ignacy Łukasiewicz scholarship (2020-2023) | NAWA | Poland

• Fully funded scholarship to study Polish language and Master degree in Polish universities

JASSO scholarship (2016-2017) | JASSO | Japan

• Fully funded scholarship to study in Japanese universities